[Music]
[Applause]
but also by finally approving i-i'm a
leave a [__] hell
[Music]
the main event accountability because we
are always listening always
understanding and delivery ha ha ha
nobody this is the chapter here [__]
melody mr. drainie
chief agency Officer burnstow
corporation Auto feedback - oh my
[Applause]
[Music]
I first like to start by say a few words
of thank you thanks to my good friend
I've made that all the ticket potential
get enough and most importantly my
agency brothers and sisters of
Prudential Viet Nam for having made 2018
a great year for potential Vietnam and
most importantly showing the people of
the dog have done better than anybody
else in Vietnam the undercommons of
Hyderabad please subscribe
I quit annoying as I read new
quantumness
so much like my camera
[Music]
[Applause]
because potential get some is one of our
surface business very focused very
dedicated serving the community in
Vietnam and all the people of Vietnam
know that is too much time I find out
who's also our thang much accepted for
all the valley yet Google account I
I want to talk about one is if you
already here and oh you've done well but
2018 is now history well what would you
say I know Mankato South 2009 did not do
thing like
[Music]
it's incredible I think we should focus
thank you
[Music]
I was a little tight in lollipop no Tina
Envy
who's ready happy this morning that is
[Music]
anticipated new you feeling good that I
can find time for any I think I've got
is not about just production but is
about professionalism and be a whole
person serving the community that you
work for and we are completing a phase I
sold my MD Athenian
together now so that Marcia that we have
got more immunity than the year before
so it's all employee business
now tour this year that there will be
another record at potential Vietnam
movie in terms of the total number of
every qualified and I look forward to
seeing as many of you here becoming a
winner so she took the keys Wow my
pleasure
[Applause]
this is something that is not just in
Prudential Vietnam by name is thing I've
done and put together as a TV shake
novices initiative process of important
Club across all our markets called a
nightclub the purpose of a nightclub is
to ensure not just consistent idea what
we are serving the protection of the
people when you were any particular
there were several protected
I would love to see the next time we do
the conference all the heads in very
closely I look forward to being part of
the teeth in Vietnam I didn't hear many
many times and I'm always very inspired
by the vision
[Music]
[Applause]
all my brothers and sisters of Vietnam
will become part of life club and
encourage every one of your products and
ages to become a member of the ok
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]